doi.org 2010-06-26

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

The International DOI Foundation (IDF), which produces this site, does not collect personally identifying information about individuals who visit this web site. Our logs collect and store only domain names or IP addresses, dates and times of visits, and the pages visited. Data from the logs may be used to measure the number of visitors to the site. 

The IDF sponsors both public and private web-based mailing lists, both for discussion and to distribute news and important information to interested parties. Subscribers may join and leave the subscriber lists using an automated mail list program or by sending a request to contact@doi.org. The mailing lists are used for no other purpose than to disseminate news and encourage the exchange of ideas. 

A 'cookie pusher' mechanism runs on this website in support of specific services offered by library affiliate members of [CrossRef](http://www.crossref.org/) that have chosen to participate in [CrossRef's local linking program](http://www.crossref.org/03libraries/16lib_how_to.html). Cookies are not offered to visitors to this website, nor are they used by this website for any purpose.

Individuals may decide to send email to contact@doi.org containing comments about the site or requests for information, in which they may include personally identifying information. That information is used only to enable the IDF staff to respond. 

Information gathered via forms, in particular registration forms made available for those parties wishing to join the IDF or register for an upcoming workshop, is never released outside of the organization. 

If you believe that our website has collected incorrect information, or if you would like to dispute any information, please contact us at contact@doi.org. 

The IDF does not control the privacy policies of any other sites to which we provide hyperlinks. Voluntarily disclosing personal information on sites hyperlinked to / from this site would be done at your own risk. 

Updated 26 September 2007
